<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content="<p>Learn about trommel screens, a type of equipment used in material sorting and processing. Perfect for separating materials efficiently.</p><p>Discover how a drum-shaped Trommel Screen separates materials by size, perfect for mining operations and waste management.</p><p>A motor powers the trommel screen, a machine used to separate materials by size. Learn more about this essential component here.</p><p>Discover how a hopper is used in a trommel screen to efficiently separate materials and improve the screening process.</p><p>Discover the fines outlet on a trommel screen - essential for separating fine materials from larger ones efficiently.</p><p>Learn about the operation of a trommel screen - a versatile piece of equipment used in various industries for separating materials efficiently.</p><p>Material feeding is integral to the functioning of a trommel screen, ensuring efficient separation and processing of materials.</p><p>Learn about the screening process with a trommel screen, used for separating materials efficiently in various industries.</p><p>Learn how a trommel screen separates materials efficiently, making it an essential tool for various industries.</p><p>Discover the various applications of trommel screens in industries like mining, waste management, and composting. Learn more about this versatile equipment.</p><p>Discover how trommel screens are revolutionizing the mining industry with their efficient and versatile screening capabilities.</p><p>Learn about trommel screens, a key tool in waste management for separating materials and improving recycling efficiency.</p><p>Discover how trommel screens are used in the composting process to efficiently separate materials and create high-quality compost.</p><p>Discover the benefits of using a trommel screen for efficient material separation and processing. Find out how this equipment can improve your operations.</p><p>Learn about the effectiveness of trommel screens for efficiently screening large volumes of material in various industries.</p><p>Learn how a trommel screen offers versatility in handling various materials, making it a valuable tool for many industries.</p><p>Trommel screens have low maintenance requirements, making them a cost-effective and efficient solution for separating materials.</p><p>Discover the key factors to consider when choosing a trommel screen for your screening needs. Find out how this equipment can benefit your operation.</p><p>Learn about the size and capacity needed for a trommel screen, essential for efficient material sorting and processing in various industries.</p><p>Learn about the various types of materials that can be processed using a trommel screen. Find out more about this versatile screening equipment now!</p><p>Learn how budget constraints can impact the decision to invest in a trommel screen for efficient waste sorting and recycling processes.</p>">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/grindercrusherscreenlogo1.jpg"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Roboto:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
.uab53359f8aa3761129e9c80116bf06c5 p,.uab53359f8aa3761129e9c80116bf06c5 span,.uab53359f8aa3761129e9c80116bf06c5 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
.w5fccaf3e7922f56980bdb1be0a258b86 a,.uab53359f8aa3761129e9c80116bf06c5 a{
color:#070707!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
.btn-md{
padding: 14.6px 30.5px;
border-radius: 0;
}
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
.d212f826e77c697757f0c9511cf982d09:hover{
box-shadow: 0 50.3px 50px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
.nav-item{
padding-left:8.4px;
padding-right:7.9px;
padding-top:4.9px;
padding-bottom:5px;
}
a:hover{
color:#ff0000;background:#000000!important;
}
.nav-link{
color: #000000;

}
footer{
background:#121212;
color:#ffffff;
}
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
.w5fccaf3e7922f56980bdb1be0a258b86 p,.w5fccaf3e7922f56980bdb1be0a258b86 a,.w5fccaf3e7922f56980bdb1be0a258b86 span,.w5fccaf3e7922f56980bdb1be0a258b86 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
.navbar a{
font-size: 17.6px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
*{
font-family: 'Roboto', sans-serif;
}
.uab53359f8aa3761129e9c80116bf06c5 a{
font-size:16px;
}
.ce4da32abb3965ad7bf368a6fc953bd4d{
background-color:#ff0505!important;
border-color:#ff0505!important;
color:#000000!important;
}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar-expand-lg navbar">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="index.html"  ><img alt="img/grindercrusherscreenlogo1.jpg" src="img/grindercrusherscreenlogo1.jpg"  width="150px" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="navbar-collapse collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="align-items-center navbar-nav ml-auto d-flex"><li class="nav-item"><a class="ee1dc0192d9d9520aa8b88ad5ca4720d6 nav-link" href="news.html" rel="nofollow" >News</a></li>
  
<li class="nav-item dropdown ">
<a class="dropdown-toggle ee1dc0192d9d9520aa8b88ad5ca4720d6 nav-link" href="index.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">What Is A Trommel Screen</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="index.html"  >What Is A Trommel Screen</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="drum.html"  >Drum</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="motor.html"  >Motor</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="hopper.html"  >Hopper</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="fines-outlet.html"  >Fines outlet</a>
  
<li class="nav-item dropdown ">
<a class="ee1dc0192d9d9520aa8b88ad5ca4720d6 nav-link dropdown-toggle" href="operation-of-a-trommel-screen.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Operation of a Trommel Screen</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="operation-of-a-trommel-screen.html"  >Operation of a Trommel Screen</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="material-feeding.html"  >Material feeding</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="screening-process.html"  >Screening process</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="separation-of-materials.html"  >Separation of materials</a>
  
<li class=" nav-item dropdown">
<a class="nav-link dropdown-toggle ee1dc0192d9d9520aa8b88ad5ca4720d6" href="applications-of-trommel-screens.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Applications of Trommel Screens</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="applications-of-trommel-screens.html"  >Applications of Trommel Screens</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="mining-industry.html"  >Mining industry</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="waste-management.html"  >Waste management</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="composting.html"  >Composting</a>
  
<li class="nav-item dropdown ">
<a class="dropdown-toggle nav-link ee1dc0192d9d9520aa8b88ad5ca4720d6" href="advantages-of-using-a-trommel-screen.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Advantages of Using a Trommel Screen</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="advantages-of-using-a-trommel-screen.html"  >Advantages of Using a Trommel Screen</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="efficiency-in-screening-large-volumes.html"  >Efficiency in screening large volumes</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="versatility-in-handling-various-materials.html"  >Versatility in handling various materials</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="low-maintenance-requirements.html"  >Low maintenance requirements</a>
  
<li class="dropdown nav-item ">
<a class="nav-link ee1dc0192d9d9520aa8b88ad5ca4720d6 dropdown-toggle" href="factors-to-consider-when-choosing-a-trommel-screen.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Factors to Consider When Choosing a Trommel Screen</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="factors-to-consider-when-choosing-a-trommel-screen.html"  >Factors to Consider When Choosing a Trommel Screen</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="size-and-capacity-needed.html"  >Size and capacity needed</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="type-of-material-being-processed.html"  >Type of material being processed</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="budget-constraints.html"  >Budget constraints</a>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="ee1dc0192d9d9520aa8b88ad5ca4720d6 nav-link" rel=nofollow href="about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li><li class="nav-item">
<a class="ce4da32abb3965ad7bf368a6fc953bd4d btn-md btn" href="https://www.grindercrusherscreen.com/pages/contact-us" rel="nofollow">Contact Us</a>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for GrinderCrusherScreen</h1>
<p>At GrinderCrusherScreen one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by GrinderCrusherScreen and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: https://www.grindercrusherscreen.com/</p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in GrinderCrusherScreen. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, GrinderCrusherScreen, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>GrinderCrusherScreen follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of GrinderCrusherScreen.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on GrinderCrusherScreen, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that GrinderCrusherScreen has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>GrinderCrusherScreen's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>GrinderCrusherScreen does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
GrinderCrusherScreen</br>
(770) 433-2670</br>
1772 Corn Rd</br>
Smyrna</br>
GA</br>
https://www.grindercrusherscreen.com/</br>
Sales@GrinderCrusherScreen.com</br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="py-4 pt-5 container" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3">
<p>GrinderCrusherScreen</p>
<p>Phone : (770) 433-2670</p>
<p>Email : Sales@GrinderCrusherScreen.com</p>
<p>City : Smyrna</p>
<p>State : GA</p>
<p>Zip : 30080</p>
<p>Address : 1772 Corn Rd</p>
<p><a class="ee1dc0192d9d9520aa8b88ad5ca4720d6" href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/WJM2eCyZzhKaiewk9" rel="nofollow"> Google Business Profile</a></p>
<p>Company Website : <a class="ee1dc0192d9d9520aa8b88ad5ca4720d6" href="https://www.grindercrusherscreen.com/" rel="nofollow">https://www.grindercrusherscreen.com/</a></p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3"><p><a class="ee1dc0192d9d9520aa8b88ad5ca4720d6" href="sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="ee1dc0192d9d9520aa8b88ad5ca4720d6" href="privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="ee1dc0192d9d9520aa8b88ad5ca4720d6" href="about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
</p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3">
<div>
<p>Follow us</p>
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/GrinderCrusherScreen/" class="u3d1e12348a832d7f344605e43ff4b359 facebook" rel="nofollow"><i class="fa fa-facebook"></i></a>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCGLgP54hLfx5XaFQLlJJIpQ" class="youtube u3d1e12348a832d7f344605e43ff4b359" rel="nofollow"><i class="fa fa-youtube"></i></a>
</div>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
